campusinteraction.com 2002-04-03

# Privacy Statement

> Campus Interaction is committed to making all our products, materials and information accessible to those with disabilities. To obtain a document or information in an alternate format, please call 616-353-6727 or 616-267-2629 or email [alternateformat@campusinteraction.com](mailto:alternateformat@campusinteraction.com)
> 
> _This statement was last updated on October 24, 2001_

> Campus Interaction collects certain information about users of its corporate Web site, Campusinteraction.com, via features and services of this site. It is important to us that you understand our information collection practices and policies and that you are aware of how we use information that we collect. 
> 
> You do not need to provide us with personal information in order to visit Campusinteraction.com, but you may need to provide certain personal information in order to access certain site features and services, including our Campus Interaction newsletter and the Campus Interaction listserv. The following paragraphs explain what kind of information we collect and how we use it. 
> 
> Campus Interaction collects certain generic information about all users of its Campusinteraction.com Web site and about their machines. We collect this information in the aggregate and an individual user's usage pattern cannot be identified from the aggregation. Information of this type includes — but is not limited to — your IP address, browser type and language, the last location you visited before entering Campusinteraction.com and whether certain scripts are enabled. We also collect information about the activities you engage in on our site.

> Campus Interaction uses some of this information, such as browser type and language, to provide you with the optimal viewing experience as you visit our site. We gather information relating to the activities you engage in when you visit our site in order to assess how people use the Campusinteraction.com Web site and to enhance the services and content that appear on the site.   
>  Although we will use this aggregate information primarily for internal purposes, we may disclose aggregate statistics regarding site usage to partners and other third parties and for other lawful purposes. Disclosures of this type will not contain any user-specific information and the aggregation cannot be manipulated to reveal information about an individual user.Campus Interaction uses a browser feature called a "cookie" on the Campusinteraction.com home page. Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to your computer's memory for record-keeping purposes. We use the cookie on the home page of Campusinteraction.com to help us show you certain messages about Campus Interaction and prevent us from showing messages that you have already seen. If you have chosen not to accept cookies on your computer, you can still visit our site and participate in our listserv and newsletter services. 
> 
>   
>  Campus Interaction does collect personal information about Campusinteraction.com users who wish to participate in certain services or offerings or to utilize certain features. For example, in order to participate in the Campus Interaction listserv, you will need to provide us with your name and email address. At the point of collection we will always explain what personal information we need in order to provide a service or feature to you and why we need to collect it.

> Unless you give us your permission, we will not pass personal information gathered in this way to third parties, except in the following circumstances: 
>
>> In limited circumstances, we may disclose personal information to our agents and subcontractors that assist us in fulfillment. For example, if you choose to receive the Campus Interaction newsletter, we would pass your email address to a third party that we use to assist us in sending the newsletter to you. In each case, our agents and subcontractors are contractually obligated to (i) keep such information completely confidential; (ii) use the information only for the limited purpose for which they were retained; and (iii) destroy or return the information to us at the conclusion of our work.
>> 
>> We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Campus Interaction; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Campus Interaction, Inc. or of the users of the Campus Interaction system; or (iii) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Campus Interaction users or the public.
>> 
>> In limited circumstances, we may also disclose personal information if we inform you that we intend to do so when we collect the information.
> 
> If you would like to receive the Campus Interaction newsletter, you will need to give us your name, school, title and email address. We may ask for additional information that you are welcome but not required to provide. In every such email, we will provide instructions on how to unsubscribe from these communications.

> If you volunteer personal information, such as your school affiliation and title, we may aggregate this information in order to analyze visitor trends. Although we will use these aggregates for internal research purposes, we may disclose aggregate information regarding site usage to third parties. These aggregates cannot be manipulated to reveal an individual's personal information.   
>  All personal information collected by the Campus Interaction system is stored on secure servers and is protected using industry standard methods such as firewalls and encryption.

> Campusinteraction.com is not directed to children under the age of 13.

> While we strive to protect your privacy, Campus Interaction cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us through publicly accessible channels and you send such transmissions at your own risk. We advise you to act carefully and responsibly online, maintain the secrecy of passwords and account information and be aware of the risks and responsibilities of online usage. 
> 
> Campus Interaction will update this privacy statement to reflect our current information-gathering and usage practices and policies and will update the date at the top of this page for your information. We will post all changes to this policy on this page and we reserve the right to change this policy at any time. This privacy policy covers only our information gathering practices on Campusinteraction.com. 
> 
> If you have questions about this policy or are interested in the privacy policies for our products, please contact us at [privacy@campusinteraction.com](mailto:privacy@campusinteraction.com).  
>
